dymo.com 2000-03-04

# Notices

Esselte's Privacy and Security Policy

This site has been designed with your privacy, security and convenience in mind.

  * **You're in control of how your information is used:  
**We will not rent or sell your name or personal information to any third party. (more) 
  * **This site provides you with the one of the safest and most secure web experiences possible:  
**All of your transactions at this site are secure. (more) 
  * **You will be notified of any substantial changes to our policy:  
**Since offerings and technologies change, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy at any time. (more)

**You're in control of how your information is used  
**We will not rent or sell your name or personal information to any third party without your permission.

If you use our ordering system to purchase products from one of our dealers, or other third parties, we may provide them with your name, address and other non-financial information to help them to serve you. This site has the ability to store such information to save you from having to re-enter it on a subsequent visit to our site. If you would rather we do not store this data you will have the ability to edit your account details so that this information is not kept on file after use.

Financial information such as credit card details that you enter whilst ordering are not stored on this web server after your order has been processed.

If you have set up an account with us or entered one of our contests, we may occasionally update you via email of special opportunities. If you would rather not be alerted to such opportunities, you have the ability to opt out by editing your account details to say so.

We may share statistical or demographic information with our marketing partners, advertisers, or other third-parties. This information is in the form of statistics or purchase demographics and is never connected to an individual person.

If you detect any inaccuracy in your account or personal information, we will be happy to make any changes you deem appropriate. The My Profile form enables you to review and then modify the information we have on file for you.

_Return to theTOP_

**This site provides you with one of the safest and most secure web experiences possible**  
All of your transactions at this site are secure.

Our secure server encrypts all of your personal information (including name, address and other details) so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. When you enter this information it is captured on a page that uses the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol by default. To ensure that your credit card information is even more secure, we store it on a server that is not accessible from the Internet. Esselte also uses a Digital Secure Server ID from VeriSign to provide you with high quality protection on the Internet.

Only authorized Esselte employees are permitted to have access to your personal information and such access is limited by need. In addition, any company with which Esselte contracts to be our agent in conducting our business is required to adhere to confidentiality agreements to ensure that your information remains safe and secure.

In the unlikely event that an error results in an unauthorized use of your credit card, most banks either cover all of the resultant charges or limit your liability. (Check your credit card agreement for details.) If the bank does not cover this additional liability, Esselte will cover it, provided that the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted from an error of Esselte in connection with purchases made on an Esselte-owned site, and not through any fault or omission of your own.

All of our online partners with a single-click link from this site, and all of those with whom we may share data when you place an order through our ordering system have a similar policy, but you should check their policy statements before supplying further personal information on their site. Other resellers listed in this site's dealer locator system may operate websites with a different policy to this site. You should always check their policy statements carefully before supplying them with any personal information.

_Return to theTOP_

**You will be notified of any substantial changes to our policy**  
Since offerings and technologies change, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of our policy at any time. If policy changes are substantial, we will notify each of our customers individually through email, and provide an opportunity to delete or amend account details. Please check back here for changes.

_Return to theTOP_

**We welcome your comments  
**This site is controlled and operated by Esselte Office Products, Waterside House, Cowley Business Park, Uxbridge, UB8 2HR, England. Email: [esselte_global_web@esselte.com](mailto:esselte_global_web@esselte.com).   
Please contact us if you require further policy information.
Esselte's Privacy and Security Policy

This site has been designed with your privacy, security and convenience in mind.

  * **You're in control of how your information is used:  
**We will not rent or sell your name or personal information to any third party. (more) 
  * **This site provides you with the one of the safest and most secure web experiences possible:  
**All of your transactions at this site are secure. (more) 
  * **You will be notified of any substantial changes to our policy:  
**Since offerings and technologies change, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy at any time. (more)

**You're in control of how your information is used  
**We will not rent or sell your name or personal information to any third party without your permission.

If you use our ordering system to purchase products from one of our dealers, or other third parties, we may provide them with your name, address and other non-financial information to help them to serve you. This site has the ability to store such information to save you from having to re-enter it on a subsequent visit to our site. If you would rather we do not store this data you will have the ability to edit your account details so that this information is not kept on file after use.

Financial information such as credit card details that you enter whilst ordering are not stored on this web server after your order has been processed.

If you have set up an account with us or entered one of our contests, we may occasionally update you via email of special opportunities. If you would rather not be alerted to such opportunities, you have the ability to opt out by editing your account details to say so.

We may share statistical or demographic information with our marketing partners, advertisers, or other third-parties. This information is in the form of statistics or purchase demographics and is never connected to an individual person.

If you detect any inaccuracy in your account or personal information, we will be happy to make any changes you deem appropriate. The My Profile form enables you to review and then modify the information we have on file for you.

_Return to theTOP_

**This site provides you with one of the safest and most secure web experiences possible**  
All of your transactions at this site are secure.

Our secure server encrypts all of your personal information (including name, address and other details) so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. When you enter this information it is captured on a page that uses the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol by default. To ensure that your credit card information is even more secure, we store it on a server that is not accessible from the Internet. Esselte also uses a Digital Secure Server ID from VeriSign to provide you with high quality protection on the Internet.

Only authorized Esselte employees are permitted to have access to your personal information and such access is limited by need. In addition, any company with which Esselte contracts to be our agent in conducting our business is required to adhere to confidentiality agreements to ensure that your information remains safe and secure.

In the unlikely event that an error results in an unauthorized use of your credit card, most banks either cover all of the resultant charges or limit your liability. (Check your credit card agreement for details.) If the bank does not cover this additional liability, Esselte will cover it, provided that the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted from an error of Esselte in connection with purchases made on an Esselte-owned site, and not through any fault or omission of your own.

All of our online partners with a single-click link from this site, and all of those with whom we may share data when you place an order through our ordering system have a similar policy, but you should check their policy statements before supplying further personal information on their site. Other resellers listed in this site's dealer locator system may operate websites with a different policy to this site. You should always check their policy statements carefully before supplying them with any personal information.

_Return to theTOP_

**You will be notified of any substantial changes to our policy**  
Since offerings and technologies change, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of our policy at any time. If policy changes are substantial, we will notify each of our customers individually through email, and provide an opportunity to delete or amend account details. Please check back here for changes.

_Return to theTOP_

**We welcome your comments  
**This site is controlled and operated by Esselte Office Products, Waterside House, Cowley Business Park, Uxbridge, UB8 2HR, England. Email: [esselte_global_web@esselte.com](mailto:esselte_global_web@esselte.com).   
Please contact us if you require further policy information.
